Her name is Soledad.
We're gonna get married.
She was tending bar
at some shithole
in El Paso called El Hueco.
- I want to work.
- Yeah.
And I've wasted enough time.
I have a Cessna Caravan
waiting in a hangar
at Fairfax Airport.
All I need is someone to fly her.
You know I fucking love you. right?
I'm glad you're here.
I'm supposed to be
back by morning.
Or at least call Jerome.
Your days of slaving for
that Jheri curl motherfucker
are over.
- Hell nah.
- Okay. sh... Cissy.
Drunk. high. sober.
I don't give a damn.
Nobody wants you here.
Get them all out of here now!
I ain't movin'!
I ain't...
My customers don't pay
in large bills.
You ever hear of a bank?
What you lookin' for?
We got what you need. man...
What!
We got to send a message. right?
By killing a bunch of old folks
and fuckin' kids. my nigger?
We can't let these
motherfuckin' wetbacks kill
our people and walk around
like ain't shit happened.
So you gonna go and kill
the first Mexican you see?
That's what you do. man.
I always knew you wasn't built
for that shit. Saint.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey.
What's up?
And a merry Christmas to you.
Okay.
So. uh.
not like I needed
a reminder. but here.
I got something for ya.
Jason Peters?
Nice to meet you.
And you're 47 years old.
It's a joke.
So. uh. show up at that address.
The one on the card there.
Tuesday.
Please don't show up an hour
early to that one.
Right.
And you got a suit?
Something nice to wear?
- I can get one.
- All right.
Don't cheap out on the shoes.
Hey. where'd you even get these?
Gotta know who to ask.
I'll see ya.
Jason motherfuckin' Peters?
Hi.
You got to be Cissy.
I'm Nia.
We spoke on the phone?
I'm an advocate for the homeless
at the Edgewood Shelter.
What happened?
Cops were clearing an empty lot
in an effort to make
our city pretty
in time for the Olympics.
Alton didn't want to leave.
- When?
- Six days ago.
And he's been here ever since?
They wanted
to release him today.
But he has two broken ribs.
cuts that need cleaning.
stitches.
Send him back out there
and he'll die of infection.
How'd you get my number?
You're his emergency contact
at the VA.
He had his vet ID on him.
He's through the worst
of the detox.
But if he gets put back
on the street
chances are he runs
right back to the bottle.
Chances are good of that
no matter where he goes.
Look. I don't know
y'all's situation.
but he needs a safe place
right now.
You don't know
what you're asking me.
That's true.
I don't.
Hey. Kev.
sorry about the other day.
You gotta do what
you gotta do. right?
What's up y'all?
- What. Santa come early?
- God. I hope it's sandwiches.
Them ain't no sandwiches.
You know we can't move the
product we already got. right?
And I cut my thumb.
It was gross.
Blood everywhere.
We ain't got to move it all.
It's just how much I gotta buy.
all right?
So hire more cookers.
- And more dealers.
- We've been through this.
And you still ain't listening.
Look. we can't
risk giving away...
The recipe. the recipe.
Franklin.
My hair stank and my feet hurt.
- I'm sorry.
- If you want this rocked up.
wake up the motherfucker
snoring on the couch.
I can't do this alone.
Hm.
- Hey. I'm out too.
- What?
Gonna go see my girl.
Who I could see in here
if you would allow her to cook.
You want some good news?
Sure.
Pretty good. right?
That's real good.
Damn.
It was easy actually.
The Valley is thirsty. amigo.
You want three this time?
Damn... whoa. oh.
Yeah.
It's good. man.
Same deal.
60/40.
Rad. man.
Thank you.
Look. I know of
a party going on right now.
This will sell like hotcakes.
No. you gotta help me cook
this shit. Rob.
No. trust me. brother.
You want me at this party.
I'll catch you later. okay?
Whoo.
Fuck.
Did you get lost?
Sorry.
- Ready?
- Uh-huh.
Let's do it.
Hey. Amira.
We're all set.
Right this way.
Gentleman. please have a seat.
So I assume Mr. Thompson
has made you aware
of our rate of exchange?
Yeah.
Reed explained it to me.
Good. I find it's the best
way to describe how we. uh.
convert and move our assets
without getting into certain
un-pleasantries.
Right.
So. uh...
how would you like to have
your account entered?
In your name?
Yes. please.
Yeah.
And what identification would
you like to use to access it?
Yeah. um. I'll be using my. uh.
my North Dakota drivin' license.
Here you go.
I like your statue.
Thank you.
It's Persian jade.
Yeah. my mom's had one just
like it when I was a kid.
Not that color. but a lion.
I dropped it.
She was...
She was mad.
You know what?
You should take it.
Nah. it's...
No. no. please.
Think of it as a. uh.
token of our future together.
Give it to your mother
and watch her smile.
Thank you.
Now. in order to best
understand how to protect
your assets we should discuss
how you plan to disperse them.
If it's just cash withdrawals.
that is a process we can handle
for you here. in house.
But. um. I was thinking
of maybe investing.
You know. real estate?
Oh.
If acquisitions are
your final goal.
may I make a recommendation?
For an extra 6%. we can
create a corporation for you.
In your name. but overseas.
This will allow you to acquire
assets within the United States
without drawing
any unwanted attention.
- And where would this bank be?
- It's not a bank.
It's just a place where
your business will be based.
And there are several options.
but at this point in time
and for a variety of reasons.
I recommend Jersey.
Y... you could set an overseas
account up in New Jersey?
Forgive me.
Jersey is an island
5x9 miles in size
off the coast of France.
So would you like to proceed
with this?
And this. um. extra 6%...
Seems like... seems like a lot.
Of course.
Take your time.
It's not
that I don't understand.
Look. it's the same rate I get.
It's the exact same deal.
Yeah. no offense. Reed.
but I still don't actually
know you.
Thought this is what I wanted.
Now that I'm here.
handing all my money over
to another dude I don't know.
trusting that all this is legit.
I don't know.
It doesn't seem right.
I have...
what some people might call
control issues.
And I always have
and since I was a kid. really.
but the simple truth is that
I can't do everything alone.
So I have to empower the people
that I choose to work with.
See. it's not just
about being in charge.
It's about deciding how you
want to be in charge.
Look. you wanna walk
out of here right now.
that's fine.
I understand.
I'll keep taking your fives
and your ones.
I don't care.
It makes no difference to me.
But what you have to decide...
is just how big you want
your business to become.
And how much control you are
willing to cede
to get it there.
We got a problem.
Shit.
We're short.
Short what?
What you talkin' bout "short"?
Money.
From the trucks.
Almost five grand.
Come on. boy.
You telling me you get yo balls
all twisted up over five grand?
It's not the money.
It's the principle.
This ain't no corner boy shit.
It's one of us.
You stealin' from me. nigga?
I know your ass ain't askin' me
so who you think took it?
I don't know.
My advice?
Let that shit be.
Assume whoever took it need it.
Eh?
We got a problem.
These cats got took.
Couple fat motherfuckers
jacked us.
They stole the take
and the rock.
How much they get?
150 cash.
Couple dozen rocks.
We tried to stop them.
but there was four of 'em.
They was big.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
They for real.
Y'all good?
Need a doctor or something?
Nah. we straight.
Hazard pay.
Go get yourselves cleaned up.
Come back whenever you ready.
All right?
Hm.
What?
Fuck. you mean "what"?
People talkin'.
Since Delroy and Victor.
feel like maybe you ain't
got people back.
Peaches.
Call your guy.
Tell him we need some help.
All right?
Teddy.
You got a tree.
Hm?
Yes. Matthew.
I thought maybe we were lacking
on Christmas spirit.
- You even got lights.
- Yeah.
Strung 'em myself.
What's with the bag?
It's gonna go home.
Didn't want Dad to be alone
for Christmas.
Oh. yeah.
Yeah.
That's great.
Enjoy.
You could come with.
Christmas with the old man.
- Mm-hmm.
- Negative.
Well I can fly you
to D.C.. spend it
with Julia and Paul.
Uh. they're actually gonna go
up to her family's place
for the week in Vermont.
So I'll drop you there.
Hm?
I'm not...
actually welcome.
It's a Catholic family
and all. so they weren't
exactly thrilled
about the divorce.
Huh.
I didn't realize that you had
filed the paperwork already.
Come on.
You hated that I got married.
Yeah. well I mean I hate
the idea of marriage
as an institution more than
yours specifically.
Did you guys discuss custody?
- Holy fuck.
- What?
Um.
Don't leave.
- What's wrong?
- I might have a problem.
- What kind of a problem?
- Can you give me an hour
or two and then you can go?
Teddy.
Please?
Thank you.
Hey. baby. you back?
Hey.
I want the combination.
Say what?
To the safe.
Shit.
You in need?
What you want?
500. G?
What I want is to not have
my shit doled out to me
like I'm an infant
on a fuckin' allowance.
You ain't got to take
that tone with me.
I asked you how much
you want. right?
Just say the number.
What's the problem. Jerome?
What. you don't trust me?
Or you just think
I'm not good enough?
You just comin' off kinda
ungrateful like I ain't...
Nah. that ain't what this is.
Wait a minute. I took you in.
- Took me in?
- Remember that?
When they had tossed
your ass to the side?
I done everything for you.
I ain't even want to be
a part of this game.
I did this shit for you.
Listen to me.
I want what
I have fucking earned
and you gonna give it to me.
No.
I ain't giving you shit.
What you need to do is lay
your ass down.
so you can get your head right.
You know what?
You right.
I do need to lay down.
Next to somebody else.
So go and do that then
'cause I'm tired
of the bullshit.
And I ain't got time
for you. Jerome.
'cause this is it!
I'm done.
You ain't done with shit.
You think that old bitch can
satisfy you the way I do?
She can do ten times
what you ever could.
And you can take that
combination and all that money
and shove it right up
your fat. lazy ass.
'Cause I'm out.
Gone.
And you ain't never gonna
forget the day
you let the best thing
that's ever gonna happen to you
walk the fuck out the door.
Hey. buddy.
Hey. can I ask what you guys
doing out here?
'Cause I live nearby.
Support structures
for the Olympics.
The Olympics?
Wow.
What. uh... what events?
I don't know.
Shooting. I think?
Cool.
So. um. how much longer you
guys think you'll be?
It's just kind of loud.
you know?
Whole place will be
dug up... two days?
Two days.
Oh. shit.
Must have you guys working
like all night. right?
Not all night but pretty close.
Look. guy. I got
a million things to do. so...
Oh. yeah.
Yeah. yeah.
Thank you.
How you know this dude again?
He was in my platoon.
Nothin' to worry about.
I look worried?
You always look worried.
How's your mom?
Heard she was sick.
She go to the hospital?
Yeah.
Shit.
You got insurance?
Couple of days in the hospital.
you out a few Gs.
Need a loan or somethin'?
All right.
Ho. ho. ho. bitches.
You lookin' well. my brother.
Frank. Kit.
The boy wonder.
How you doin'. young Don?
Got some merch for us?
Ain't much for foreplay. huh?
Nah. he's fuck.
I guess we'll get to it.
This guy ever tell you
why we call him Peaches?
Yeah. something about likin'
them peaches in a can
with syrup and some shit.
Like 'em?
That's all my boy ate.
Listen. on the real.
this nigga's shit smelled
like my nana's pie.
Oh. come on. man.
Merry Christmas. motherfuckers.
This is an immigration raid.
muchachos.
Have a seat.
Hands up right now!
- Get away from there!
- Hands behind your back!
On the floor right now!
- Hey. shut up.
- Hey. they're legal!
- Hey. those two.
- They're legal.
I got the paperwork.
All of you. come over here.
And these are real how?
- What do you mean?
- Wouldn't be the first time
I saw forged green cards.
I don't hire illegals.
- Yeah. I bet.
- You guys are all alike.
- Excuse me?
- I'm from a border town.
And I've had to deal with people
like you.
None of that paperwork
is fake.
Watching my father
put his office back together
after you...
Bully to your poor little
daddy but sit down and shut up.
Hey. look.
Everything here is in order.
okay. sir?
- I bet...
- Soledad.
This is how you get hard
at night.
Walking in here.
acting like a big man.
When you slip into bed next
to your fat. ugly wife.
are you gonna be thinking
about me?
Hey. hey.
You think I can't detain you?
- You can't do shit...
- Twat...
- Hey.
- Puto.
Hey!
No. no. no.
Is that the best you can do?
- Larry. what the fuck?
- Hey!
- Larry!
- Stop it!
Get off.
Get the fuck out of here.
Okay. we're going.
We're going.
All right. let's go.
Matt?
Matt!
Damn it.
He fuckin' left?
Hey. calm down.
I'm still here.
All right. thank Christ.
Listen. you gotta call dad
and just tell him you're
not gonna make it.
- Are you kidding me?
- Come on.
We don't have a lot of time!
And. uh.
you want to put some boots on
and. uh. put on anything
Slow down.
That you don't mind
getting dirty.
And. uh. get a jacket
'cause it's gonna get cold.
What you mean. she's gone?
She done. Quit.
You got her slavin'
over that stove 24/7.
What the fuck else you think
she gonna do?
That's what she said?
Ain't nothin' ever good
enough for her.
Always wanting more.
I say good riddance.
We don't need that shit.
Think this a good idea?
Think we shoulda did
this weeks ago.
Hey. why we out here. huh?
Nigga. how many times you
gonna ask?
What's up?
So he the big boss. huh?
The tall skinny one?
Yeah. that's him.
That's the Saint.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Take this.
Take the lead on this.
Hey!
- Pay attention.
- Listen up!
Y'all been doing good.
We proud of y'all.
But here's the real.
The better we do.
the more attention we get.
More people want
to take what we got.
I brought us out here today
help deal with that attention.
Now. we expect y'all
to be smart.
That mean no go shootin'
these shits off.
Bustin' off rounds
for no God damn reason.
Any of that bullshit. you out.
And you gonna get a fuckin'
beat down to boot.
Now. me and Peaches. we gonna
show you how to load 'em up.
aim. and fire 'em.
So y'all don't shoot
your dicks off
like a bunch
of motherfuckin' idiots.
Now after we finish here.
we got a little Christmas
surprise for ya.
A'ight?
All you can drink.
- Uh-huh. yeah.
- Fuck.
- Yeah!
- Smoke!
- Drink. smoke. fuck.
Motherfuckin' party.
Yeah!
- Yeah. come on.
- Yeah!
You good?
Give us your poor. your tired...
Your yearning to fuck off.
Merry fucking Christmas
pinches gringos.
Mm-hmm.
As long as I don't have
to see that anymore.
Yeah. bueno.
Merry Christmas. cuz.
Bye!
Bye. bye.
Is she now a Christmas miracle?
He treats her right.
I can see it.
Where?
Hey. good shit today.
Gettin' everybody strapped up.
You need anything else. man?
Money-wise. maybe?
You workin' hard.
I know you got that big ass
family to look after.
Your cousin want to
go to college.
That shit adds up.
If I get in need. I'll call you.
Cool?
You and Wanda.
Y'all for real?
As a heart attack.
Why?
Bring her in the cook house.
you can't dump her ass.
For real?
Hey. Wanda.
Come here.
Hey. Franklin.
You like my dress?
Very much. yeah.
Lee took me shopping
for Christmas.
I love the heart neckline.
that's the best part.
because it shows
off my collarbones.
But do you think
these shoes work?
You wanna come work for us?
Oh. my God. Franklin.
I will not let you down.
I will work so hard.
I will cook
and cook and cook...
Look. all you got to do
is keep it to yourself.
all right?
We a family here.
Gotta have trust.
Okay.
- Huh?
- You can trust me.
I promise.
Let's go dance.
Thank you. Franklin!
Step up a second. will you?
- Get it. girl!
- So how many girls
you juggling these days?
Four. five?
Since when you care how much
pussy I've been getting?
Since this pussy got expensive.
Don't that shit bleed you dry?
Not the way I do that shit.
All I'm saying is.
things are good right now.
But you might be thinking ahead.
Might wanna put some cash away
in case shit slow down.
take a turn. you know.
Hey. man.
Don't stress it.
Money been rollin' in.
That's why I took some
from the trucks
and gave it to Delroy mama.
Figure we owed 'em.
You took money
without telling me?
Yeah. man.
Gave the money
to my dead cousin's mama.
On Christmas.
I know you ain't got
no problem with that.
I got a problem
with you taking shit
without asking.
Whatever. man.
We getting paper too.
and I shouldn't have to ask you
for every little fuckin' thing.
Yeah. but I've given
you everything
you wanted. kid.
No. you haven't.
Man. you may have all these
other niggas fooled.
new guns in their pocket.
runnin' around sippin' Moet
like shit's all good.
but I know it's just
a distraction.
Band-Aid for you think
you still got us
out here acting
like fucking bitches.
We retaliate. the prison esés
be after all of us.
Pick us off one by one.
My fuckin' family.
Yours.
Is that what you want?
Nah. nah. nah.
Franklin. what I want
is for us not to be out here
actin' like cowards.
Hittin' back.
That's what I want.
You really not gonna
let this shit go?
No. and you shouldn't
neither. Saint.
Okay.
Here's a deal I'm willing
to make with you.
If you can figure out
who did it.
some real information that even
gives us a small chance
to hit back without putting
every fuckin' vato in LA on us
then we can talk about payback.
That good enough for now?
Huh?
Yeah.
That's okay.
Yeah. baby.
Right through here.
Nice dress.
Thank you.
Claudia get it for you?
She did.
What if I promise you don't have
to work in the kitchen again?
It ain't about that.
We started this.
Me and you. right here.
Hm? Remember that?
I can't do this without you.
You gonna have to try.
Merry Christmas. Franklin.
Everybody now.
Teddy. it's your verse. man.
When whatever it is
is dug up
what do you want to do with it?
Oh. Jesus Christ.
Rebury it.
Somewhere far from here.
I know that smell.
What the hell is this. Teddy?
Fuck.
It's nearly 5:00.
We don't have much time.
I thought we were moving some
kind of fucking coke stash.
How many are there?
Hm?
God damn it.
fucking talk to me...
There's two. all right?
All right?
There's two.
Who are they?
One was a drug dealer.
And the other was a woman.
And he killed her.
So you killed him.
He was a bad person.
I had no choice.
Matt.
Listen.
If we don't get them up
and out of here
before the sky gets light.
we are both
completely
and utterly fucked. okay?
Okay.
There in fucking suitcases.
You're the only person
who knows.
Literally the only person
I could have taken
with me tonight.
Look. if you want to leave.
if you want out.
that's fine.
I understand.
This was always gonna be
temporary.
You've already done
more than enough.
You awake?
Where am I?
I brought you home
from the hospital.
You're in Franklin's room.
Alton?
He friendly?
How would I know?
Picked him up at a shelter.
Said I was considering adoption.
INS thing end up doing
what you hoped?
Yeah.
Expect Larry decided to
punch me in the fucking face.
Piece of shit.
Are you kidding me?
It's fine.
At least it worked.
The ice queen
was very impressed.
She's starting to let me in.
What do you think of her?
I think she's gonna go
down in flames.
Well. you just be careful.
all right?
Wow.
That's some good advice.
You're a fuckin' ballbreaker.
Lorena. you know that?
Merry Christmas.
Feliz Navidad. Oso.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm